Huh
Hey hey hey hey
CLIK CLAK heels tap
Walkin' with my hips back
Money CLIK CLAK
CLIK CLAK CLIK CLAK CLIK CLAK
Spending money charge charge charge
Who be livin’ large large large
Walking like a boss boss boss
We make ’em talk talk talk talk
I need a van to hold all my bags
Always the first and never the last
Here with my girls we step on the scene
We do it big you know what I mean
If I say which one looks better
You say both (both) both (both)
I’m bad from any angle
Hit that pose (pose) pose (pose)
Matching tennis bracelets
Baby blue water vacations
I’ll admit that I’m so vicious
No I ain’t the one to play with
Everybody wanna know oh oh
Bitty burning up the show oh oh
Eenie meenie miney moe
Catch ’em by the toe
You ain’t even no
I’ma let it go
CLIK CLAK heels tap
Walkin' with my hips back
Money CLIK CLAK
CLIK CLAK CLIK CLAK CLIK CLAK
Spending money charge charge charge
Who be livin’ large large large
Walking like a boss boss boss
We make ‘em talk talk talk talk
CLIK CLAK heels tap
Walkin' with my hips back
Money CLIK CLAK
CLIK CLAK CLIK CLAK CLIK
Walking like a boss boss boss
We make ‘em talk talk talk talk
Get back whip that they mad
Clap clap bring that ASAP
If they all up in their feelings
that’s too bad
I be laughing to the bank in my Maybach
Left hand kiss that big rock
Tunnel vision twenty twenty top notch
Spent a milly on some fits I’m so hot
Put some ice on my wrist that’s water
I’m on it on it got it flaunt it
Got your world in my pocket
Zero hundred like Ferrari
Hit the gas
Who gon’ stop me
You love when BABYMONSTER hits
Cartier stacked up on my wrist
Flip my hair and blow a kiss
Not a dentist but I’m flossin' sis
CLIK CLAK heels tap
Mmmmm
CLIK CLIK CLAK heels tap
CLIK CLAK heels tap
Mmmmm
CLIK CLIK CLAK heels tap
Walkin' with my hips back
Money CLIK CLAK CLIK CLAK CLIK CLAK
CLIK CLIK CLAK heels tap
Walkin' with my hips back
Money CLIK CLAK CLIK CLAK
Ain’t looking back
Let’s take the lead
Go head ladies
Ain’t looking back
Let’s take the lead
Go head ladies
Here we go